Guide to the Association of Yale Alumni Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1970-2006; Accession 2018-A-0044
  - Yale College Reunions
    - Class of 1977 20th reunion, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Class of 1982 15th reunion, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Class of 1987 10th reunion, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Class of 1992 5th reunion, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Reunion follow-up, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Reunion clerks, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Bright Horizons, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Housing, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Attendance, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Multi class programs expenses, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - AYA schedule, printed material, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Class of 1928 directory, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Class of 1933 65th reunion, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Class of 1938 60th reunion, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Class of 1943 55th reunion, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Class of 1948 50th reunion, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Class of 1948 50th reunion book, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Class of 1948 installation of Bush portrait, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Class of 1953 45th reunion, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Class of 1958 40th reunion, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Class of 1963 35th reunion, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Class of 1968 30th reunion, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Class of 1978 20th reunion, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Class of 1983 15th reunion, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Class of 1988 10th reunion, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Class of 1993 5th reunion, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Reunions follow-up, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Children of Yale/Bright Horizons, 1987-1998 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Housing, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - All-class programs, planning materials, logistics, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Samples of printed materials, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - AYA schedule, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Class of 1934 65th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Class of 1939 60th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Class of 1944 55th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Class of 1949 50th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Class of 1954 45th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Class of 1959 40th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Class of 1964 35th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Class of 1969 30th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Class of 1974 25th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Class of 1979 20th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Class of 1984 15th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Class of 1989 10th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Class of 1994 5th reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Design/printing of reunion materials, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Facilities/logistics, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Reunion survey results and follow-up letters, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - General, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Catering, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Clerks/custodial, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Reunion survey, staff and head clerk evaluations, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Directories, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Morning at Yale and president's briefing and other university programs, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Budgets, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Daria's reunions (Class of 1974 25th reunion), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Children of Yale/Bright Horizons, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)